[MOCKING PENNY]
"It doesn't matter if you're cool or not.
Because I'm Penny, I'm pretty
and I can do whatever I want."
[NORMAL VOICE] "You think you're doing
a favor by being in a relationship with me."
[MOCKING PENNY] "No. I'm doing you
a favor by being in the same room as you."
Leonard, stop the car.
(Penny:)What?
(Sheldon:)I can't listen to the two of you fight
anymore.
(Sheldon:)-Come on. We're late.
-Calm down. We'll make the movie.
(Sheldon:)I believe my alarm is appropriate.
The movie starts in 17 minutes.
(Sheldon:)We'll need to make all the lights
on Colorado Boulevard.
(Sheldon:)Plus, skip the concession stand
and pre-show urination.
(Raj:)Oh, dude, I wish you had said something
before I pounded that last Red Bull.
SHELDON:
Go. Go, Power Rangers, go.
(Penny:)-Hey.
-Hey.
(Leonard:)-We're, uh, going to the movies.
-No, we're not.
(Sheldon:)We're standing in the hallway,
suffering through an awkward encounter.